Association on American Indian Affairs Records, 1851-2016 (bulk 1922-1995): Finding Aid MC147
Public Policy Papers
- Series 6: Jack Trope Legal Counsel Files, 1966-1999; 26 boxes
  - Background, 1987-1992; 1 box (Box 496)
  - Drafts of Californian Agreement, 1990; 1 box (Box 496)
  - AAIA - BIA Soc. Serv/ICW Regulations, 1990-1992; 1 box (Box 497)
  - Miscellaneous NICWA, 1992-1995; 1 box (Box 497)
  - ICWA Case Inquiries, 1995-1996; 1 box (Box 497)
  - ICWA Conferencef - Boulder, Co, 1995; 1 box (Box 497)
  - Miscellaneous ICWA Documents and Regulations, 1989-1995; 1 box (Box 497)
  - Blackfeet ICWA Agreement, 1987; 1 box (Box 497)
  - Alaska Adoption Rules, 1987-1990; 1 box (Box 497)
- Series 7: November 2005 Addition, 1007 January 12-2004; 12 boxes
  ML2005-011
  Series 7: November 2005 Addition (1990-2005) contains executive office files, publications, photographs, conference and meetings records, donor information, and other miscellaneous material.
  All records in Series 7 are closed for a period of 15 years following the date of their creation.
  - Tax Documents, 1993; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Confirmation Letters, 1992-1995; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Expense Reports, Budget, Payroll, 1992-1994; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Lease, Floor Plan, 1990 August 25; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Year End Report, 1993; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Copyright Certificates, 1985; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Tax Exemption, 1989; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Bylaws, 1987-1989; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Registration Statement, Tax Return, Budget, 1992; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Contributions, Grants, 1992; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Budget, 1990-1993; 1 box
    - 1993, 1 box (Box 451)
    - 1991, 1 box (Box 451)
    - 1992, 1 box (Box 451)
    - 1990-1991, 1 box (Box 451)
  - Year End Reports, Miscellaneous, 1986-1993; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Year End Reports, Eight Month Reports, Six Month Reports, 1957-1992; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Treasurer's Report, Balance Sheet, 1966-1985; 1 box (Box 451)
  - American Indian Arts Center, Indian and Eskimo Art of the Americas, Financial Statements, Six Month Report, 1968-1975; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Moving Expenses, 1990 September 24; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Tax, 1985-1994; 1 box
    - Returns, 1985-1994; 1 box (Box 451)
    - Income, Corporation, Financial Transactions, Support Test, 1992-1994; 1 box (Box 451)
    - Returns, 1986-1992; 1 box (Box 451)
    - Documents, Miscellaneous, 1993-1994; 1 box (Box 451)
    - Information, Documents, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, I-II,1984-1994, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 451)
  - Flute, Jerry, Faxes and Correspondence and Memos, 1994; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Correspondence, 1994; 1 box
    - Genealogy, 1994; 1 box (Box 452)
    - General Information, 1994; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Requests, 1994; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Flute, Jerry, 1994; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Josephy, Alvin M. Jr., National Support Council Prospects, 1994 October 20; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Addresses Information on National Supports Council Sent to, undated; 1 box (Box 452)
  - American Indian Religious Freedom Act, 1994; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Board of Directors Memoranda, 1994, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Helphrey, Juanita J., Resume, 1992; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Member's Fall Luncheon and Miscellaneous Contact Information, 1993; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Fundraising, 1994 January 24-March 8; 1 box
    - Committee Meeting, 1994 January 24; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Wounded Knee Memorial, 1994 March 8; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Luncheon, 1994 January 24; 1 box (Box 452)
  - National Support Council Development Campaign, 1988-1994; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Lucy Covington Award Reception, Honoree Harris, LaDonna, 1994; 1 box (Box 452)
  - American Indian Religious Freedom Project, 1993-1994; 1 box
    - Beneficia Grant Proposal, 1994; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Ford Grant Proposal, 1993; 1 box (Box 452)
    - PEW Grant Proposal, circa 1993; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Tides Foundation Proposal, 1993; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Trope, Jack, 1993-1994 November 1; 1 box
    - Materials Regarding Legal and Constitutional Issues Raised by the Department of Justice, 1993; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Mailing, Medicine Wheel and Other Issues, 1994 September 15; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Conference Call, 1994 October 10; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Medicine Wheel Coalition Fax, 1994 October 21; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Conference Call, 1994 October 19; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Medicine Wheel Coalition Fax, 1994 November 1; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Letter to Keown, Larry, Forest Supervision, 1994 July 20; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Medicine Wheel Programmatic Agreement, 1994 April 25; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Statement of Congressman Richardson on Introduction of Legislation Protecting The Religious Use of Peyote, 1994; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Native American Rights Fund Briefing Document, 1994; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Historic Preservation Fund Grants to Indian Tribes, Alaska Natives, and Native Hawaiians, 1995; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Flute, Jerry Correspondence, Steinem, Gloria, Deer, Ada E, 1994; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Kimble, Gary Niles, Correspondence, 1994 January 24; 1 box (Box 452)
  - American Indian Religious Freedom Project, Information Packet, 1993; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Native American Free Exercise of Religion Act, 1994; 1 box
    - Conference Calls, 1994 May; 1 box (Box 452)
    - Fax to Technicians Committee, 1994; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Displaced Homemakers Proposal, 1994-1995; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Trope, Jack, Mailing Miscellaneous, 1993; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Materials Regarding Legal and Constitutional Issues Raised by the Department of Justice, 1993; 1 box (Box 452)
  - Combined Federal Campaign Correspondence, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Grant Correspondence, 1994; 1 box
    - Refusal, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
    - Acceptance, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Resumes, Employment Refusal, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Kimble, Gary N Correspondence, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Fundraising Meeting Minutes, Washington, DC, 1994 April 24; 1 box (Box 453)
  - National Indian Education Association, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - AAIA Press Release, 1994 June 30; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Princeton University Library AAIA Acquisition Correspondence, 1994 August 12; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Wounded Knee Memorial Concert Event, Casella, Sonny Proposal, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Staff Reports, 1993; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Wexler, Jonathan Correspondence, 1991-1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Yetter, Bob, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Indian Affairs AAIA Newsletter, 1977-1993; 1 folder (Box 453)
  - Indian Family Defense, 1974-1975; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1993; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Indian Recipe, Fried Bread, undated; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Indian Family Summit, 1994; 1 box
    - Correspondence, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
    - Memoranda, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
    - Planning Meeting, 1994 September 30; 1 box (Box 453)
    - Sears Roebuck Proposal, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
    - Kelloggs Proposal Draft, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Keeler, Bradford, Small Business Administration, 1993-1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Kimble, Gary N., 1992-1994; 1 box
    - Away Article, 1993; 1 box (Box 453)
    - Correspondence Support for Role as Commissioner of Administration for Native Americans, 1993; 1 box (Box 453)
    - Administration for Native Americans Articles, circa 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
    - United States Department of the Interior Correspondence, 1992-1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Locke Pat Memoranda, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Minutes for Winter Board Meeting, 1990; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Fundraising, 1991 July 16-1992; 1 box
    - Training, Trainer Harry, Debra, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 453)
    - Fundraising Trip, 1992; 1 box (Box 453)
    - Raiser Job Description, undated; 1 box (Box 453)
    - Personal Procedures, 1991 July 16; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Miscellaneous Graphics, undated; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Holtshopple, Correspondence, 1994 May 24; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Film Festival, 1992; 1 box
    - Operations Committee Meeting, 1992 February 5; 1 box (Box 453)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Indian Defamation, Mascots and Nicknames, 1992-1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Education Information from Department of the Interior, 1993-1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Karras, James Correspondence, 1993; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Navajo Nation, 1993 September 3; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Native American Free Exercise of Religion Act of, 1993; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Report Cover Sheet, undated; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Board Meeting Expenses Budget, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Genealogy Packet, 1977; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Tribal Leaders Directory, 1992-1993; 1 box
    - 1992, 1 box (Box 453)
    - 1993, 1 box (Box 453)
  - 800 Number, Arrangements, undated; 1 box (Box 453)
  - AAIA Mission Statement, 1989-1990; 1 box (Box 453)
  - American Indian Religious Freedom Act, Native American Free Exercise of Religion Act, Briefing Documents, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Tribal Directory Information and Application, undated; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Belanger, Suzanne Bard Training, 1993-1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - AAIA Strategic Plan, 1989-1990; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Calendar Months, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - The Destruction of American Indian Families, undated; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Clinton, Bill, Eagle Fathers, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - Federal Recognition, 1994; 1 box (Box 453)
  - American Indian Religious Freedom Act, Miscellaneous I-IV, 1990-1991; 1 box (Box 453)
  - American India Religious Freedom Act, Miscellaneous V-VIII, 1990-1991; 1 box (Box 454)
  - Drugs and Alcohol Materials, 1985-1994; 1 box
    - Developmental Dynamics of Native Alcoholism, Alcohol Abuse Information, 1994; 1 box (Box 454)
    - National Pan-Methodist Coalition, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 454)
    - Alcoholism Paper, Population Statistics, circa 1990; 1 box (Box 454)
    - Alcohol World, Health Forum, Pamphlets, 1985-1994; 1 box (Box 454)
    - Dugs and Alcohol Bill, 1988; 1 box (Box 454)
    - American Indian Inmate Rehabilitation Plan Information, undated; 1 box (Box 454)
    - Miscellaneous, 1994; 1 box (Box 454)
  - Indian Social Services Assistance Act, 1987-1988; 1 box
    - Table of Revenues, 1987; 1 box (Box 454)
    - Summery, Bill, 1988; 1 box (Box 454)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990; 1 box (Box 454)
  - American Indian Religious Freedom Act Background, 1988-1989; 1 box (Box 454)
  - 1980-1988, 1 box (Box 454)
  - American Indian Religious Freedom Act, 1989-1991; 1 box
    - Act, undated; 1 box (Box 454)
    - General Bill, 1989-1991; 1 box (Box 454)
  - Colorado River Tribal Council, 1969-1984; 1 box (Box 454)
  - Cultural Rights, 1989; 1 box (Box 454)
  - Religious Freedom, Burial Sites, 1989-1990; 1 box (Box 455)
  - Harjo, Suzan Correspondence, 1989 March 9; 1 box (Box 455)
  - Havasupai, Religion, Mines, 1986-1988; 1 box (Box 455)
  - Fundraising, 1984-1994; 1 box
    - Foundations, 1984-1990; 1 box
      - Ford,1993, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 455)
      - Gannett,1991, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 455)
      - Hearst,1987, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 455)
      - Irvin Greif,1990-1992, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 455)
      - W. K. Kellogg, 1990; 1 box (Box 455)
      - Kerr, undated; 1 box (Box 455)
      - Albert Kunstadter Family, 1984-1987; 1 box (Box 455)
      - Lily Endowment, 1987; 1 box (Box 455)
      - Agnese N. Lindley, 1986-1989; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Major Gift Asks, undated; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Correspondence, Memoranda, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Projected Budget, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Listmark Project, 1994; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Thomson, Ruth, 1993 August 20; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Duplicate Record Reports, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Board Member Donors, 1993; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Washington, DC, 1994 April; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Lucy Covington Award, 1994 September 29; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Donor Reports, 1994 September 29; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Major Donors, New York, New Jersey, Connecticut, 1994; 1 box (Box 455)
    - United Way, 1994; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Donor Correspondence, Records, 1994; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Donor Statistics, 1993-1994; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Donations, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Committee Meetings, 1992 October 21-1993 February 17; 1 box
      - 1993 February 17, 1 box (Box 455)
      - Francesca Kress Luncheons, 1992 November 18-19; 1 box (Box 455)
      - 1992 October 21, 1 box (Box 455)
      - 1992 November 6, 1 box (Box 455)
    - Total Donations Reports, 1993 September 29; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Reports for Auditors, 1994 April; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Phone Project Reports, 1994; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Donor Information from ListMark, 1993; 1 box (Box 455)
    - To Do, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - May, John, 1992 October 23; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Sundance, 1993; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1992; 1 box
      - End of Year, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
      - Stock, 1990-1991; 1 box (Box 455)
      - Pending, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Displaced Homemaker Program, undated; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Rigoberta Menchu Dinner, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991-1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Great Lakes Communications, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Morton, Dean, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Racimo, Victoria, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Fall, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
  - Religious Freedom Background, Purpose, Budget, undated; 1 box (Box 455)
  - General Notes, 1991-1992; 1 box (Box 455)
  - Listmark, 1991-1992; 1 box (Box 455)
  - Smith, Pat, 1991-1992; 1 box
    - General Documents, 1991-1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Government, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
  - Engagement Calendar, 1993; 1 box (Box 455)
  - Printing Costs, 1992; 1 box (Box 455)
  - Foundations, Funds, 1975-1993; 1 box
    - Seventh Generation Annual Report, 1986-1989; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Elmina B. Sewall, 1990-1992; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Robert Sharp, Informational Materials, 1990-1991; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Shell Oil Company, 1975-1993; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Elizabeth Bayne Shields, 1979-1983; 1 box (Box 455)
    - Allogan Slagle, 1990 April 21; 1 box (Box 455)
  - Donor Records A-Z, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Pow Wow Trip, Donation Correspondence, Organizational Analysis, 1990-1992; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Board of Directors, 1993-1994; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Correspondence, 1995; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Financial Reports, 1993-1995; 1 box (Box 456)
  - National Charities Information Bureau, Chief Executive Financial Report, 1993-1994; 1 box (Box 456)
  - State Registration, 1993-1994; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Tax Exemption Forms, 1970-1989; 1 box (Box 456)
  - AAIA Strategic Plan, 1989-1990; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Transactions, Accounts, Budgets, Scholarships, Miscellaneous Financial Statements, 1993-1994; 1 box (Box 456)
  - American Indian and Alaska Native Ministry of the Episcopal Church, 1990; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Calendar, 1991; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Personnel Information, Board Documents, Reports, Minutes,1986-1991, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Resumes, 1992-1993; 1 box (Box 456)
  - American Indian Religious Freedom Act Coordinator Position, 1993; 1 box
    - People Contacted, 1993; 1 box (Box 456)
    - Resumes, 1993; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Josephy Event, List, Labels, 1995; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Financial Statements, Balance Sheets, 1962-1964; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Trope, Jack Correspondence, Peyote, 1990; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Hoffer, Jane, Photographer, 1992; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Airline Ticket, 1994; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Sacred Site Holistic Healing Conference report, 1996 May 18-19; 1 box (Box 456)
  - Second Annual Northern Plains Diabetes Conference, Survey Responses, 2000 December 12; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Thorpe, Dagmar, People of the Seventh Fire, undated, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 457)
  - un Death at Sand Creek: The South Winter 1864, undated, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Publications/AAIA Newsletter Indian Affairs #144 Miscellaneous, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 457)
  - AAIA Newsletters, 1977-1996; 1 folder (Box 457)
  - AAIA Library, 1999; 1 box
    - Collection Catalogues, 1999; 1 box (Box 457)
    - Status, Disposition, Donations, 1999; 1 box (Box 457)
    - Inventory, undated; 1 box (Box 457)
  - NL 149, 2001; 1 folder (Box 457)
  - Indian Affairs: newsletter #106, 1984 May; 1 folder (Box 457)
  - Indian Affairs: newsletter #107, 1984 October; 1 folder (Box 457)
  - Indian Affairs: newsletter #108, 1985 February; 1 folder (Box 457)
  - Indian Affairs: newsletter #109, 1985 September; 1 folder (Box 457)
  - Publications/ Newsletter 146-147, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 457)
  - NL 150, circa 2001 (Box 457)
  - NL 151, 2002; 1 folder (Box 457)
  - AAIA Newsletter Claims (Answered), 1995-1999; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Newsletter Input, general, 1999; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Diabetes Conference Survey Replies, Attendee Comments, 1999; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Newsletter Articles, 1997-1998; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Requests for Broadcasts, Releases, 1999; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Northern Plains Regional Indian Diabetes Invitational Conference, 1999 May 25-26; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Argus Leader Week Long Series, Publications, 2000; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Sacred Sites Holistic Healing Conference Report, 1996 May 18-19; 1 box (Box 457)
  - AAIA: Activity Reports/Updates: 1996 April, 1 box (Box 457)
  - AAIA: Activity Reports/Updates: 1996 October, 1 box (Box 457)
  - AAIA: Activity Reports/Updates: 1997 June, 1 box (Box 457)
  - AAIA: Activity Reports/Updates: 1998 March, 1 box (Box 457)
  - AAIA: Activity Reports/Updates: 1999 February, 1 box (Box 457)
  - Trope, Jack Legal Activities, 1997-1999; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Public Service Announcement, 1999; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Lucy Covington and Emily Peone Celebration, Photographs, 1994; undated; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Annual Report, 1997-2002; 1 box
    - Brochure, 1997; 1 box (Box 457)
    - 2002, 1 box (Box 457)
    - Brochure1994-1996, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 457)
    - Brochure, Materials, 1998; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Newsletter, Miscellaneous, 2002-2003; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Clark, Elizabeth Ella %tb %te Or Indian Legends of Canada ginal Contract, 1986; 1999; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Publications, 1996-2001; 1 box
    - Permissions Granted, 2000; 1 box (Box 457)
    - McClelland and Stewart, 1999; 1 box (Box 457)
    - Copyright Clearance Center, 1997 October 27; 1 box (Box 457)
    - Book Royalties, 1996-1999; 1 box (Box 457)
    - Newsletter Cost Correspondence, 2001; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Annual Report Draft, Working Papers, 1994; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Newsletter 145, Miscellaneous, 2000; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Summer Camp Correspondence, 2000; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Indian Affairs Newsletter, 1977-2000; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Scholarships, 2000 October 6-2001; 1 box
    - Young, Florence, 2000 October 6; 1 box (Box 457)
    - Crooks Memorial, 2001; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Newsletters, Photographs, Miscellaneous, 1974-1994; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Petition, 1905 January 18; 1 box (Box 457)
  - %tb %te, The American Indian icrofiche, 1943-1959; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Indian Newsletter, National Council of American Indians, 1929; 1 box (Box 457)
  - McGovern, Senator George, Wooden Legs, John, LaFarge, Oliver, Photograph, undated; 1 box (Box 457)
  - AAIA Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 2002; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Calendar of Important Native American Events, 1789-1983; 1985; 1 box (Box 457)
  - Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1996-1998; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Rhine, Gary, %tb %te, A Sacred Place irst Draft Screenplay, 1007 January 12; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Northern Plains Regional Diabetes Conference Registration List, 2000; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Indian Affairs Newsletters, 1977-2004; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Curtis, John W., Correspondence, Artwork, 2001; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Annual Meeting of Members and Annual Board Meeting, 2000 November 16-17; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Consultant, 1995-1999; 1 box
    - Slagle, Logan, 1995-1999; 1 box (Box 458)
    - Teddy, Kapono, Locke, Knight, Emerson, Lavern, 1998; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Web Page, Lawrence and Schiller, 2001; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Summer Camps, 2001-2002; 1 box
    - 2001-2002, 1 box (Box 458)
    - Approvals, Check Requests, 2001; 1 box (Box 458)
    - Photographs, 2001; 1 box (Box 458)
    - Hasinai, 2001; 1 box (Box 458)
    - Funding Requests, 2001; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Publications/Newsletter 147, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 458)
  - Publications/Newsletter 148, 2000; 1 folder (Box 458)
  - Northern Plains Regional Diabetes Conference, 2000-2002; 1 box
    - Planning, 2001; 1 box (Box 458)
    - Working, Miscellaneous, 2002; 1 box (Box 458)
    - Correspondence, 2000; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Photographs, Newsletter, Activities Program Miscellaneous, 1984; 1997; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Photographs, circa 1950-1970; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Address, Phone Lists, Census Bureau, 1992-1993; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Requests Correspondence, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Smeal, Hank, 1988-1990; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Mascot Controversy, 1992-1993; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Board of Directors Meetings, Minutes, Memoranda, 1992-1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Donation Correspondence, Memoranda, Miscellaneous, circa 1993; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Organizational Analysis, 1990; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Education Packet, Newspaper Published for Indian Students, Educator's guide, 1991; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Education Package Update, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Ferron, Robbi Correspondence, 1993; 1 box (Box 458)
  - "Destruction of Indian Families" Editor Unger, Steven, undated; 1 box (Box 458)
  - "Economies Come to Life on Indian Reservations" New York Times, 1994 July 3; 1 box (Box 458)
  - American Indian Religious Freedom Act Amendments, Congressional Legislators, 1993; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Flute, Jerry Correspondence, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Ortiz, Alfonso Notes, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Mobil, Adams, Rex Correspondence, 1994 May 26; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Computer, 1990-1992; 1 box
    - Software list, 1992; 1 box (Box 458)
    - Hardware, Receipts, 1990; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Aids Article, Correspondence, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Tiger, Lise, Reebok Human Rights Award, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Informational Pamphlet, circa 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Prospect Letters, 1991-1993; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Appeal Letter Drafts, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Fundraising Film Proposal, Smeal Foundation, 1994 July 7; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Chace Fund Correspondence, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Casino Appeals, 1994-1995; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Donor Statistics Memorandum, 1994 January 26; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Fundraising Memoranda, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Giftmaker Correspondence, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Direct Mail Schedule, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - National Voter Registration Act Pamphlet, 1993; 1 box (Box 458)
  - New York Fundraiser, 1994 September 29; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Public Service Announcement, Celebrity Donner Correspondence, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Jules and Doris Stein Foundation, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Ford Foundation, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - National Indian Family Summit Materials, Address Lists, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - New York University Forum, 1994; 1 box (Box 458)
  - Josephy, Alvin Event, 1995 march 9, 1 box (Box 458)
  - Benefit Concerts, 1956; 1 box (Box 459)
  - Music Industry Correspondence, Itinerary, Address Lists, 1995; 1 box (Box 459)
  - Medicine Wheel Coalition Funding Proposal, 1994 December 7; 1 box (Box 459)
  - Corporate Contact Lists, Program to Seek Corporate Support, 1994; 1 box (Box 459)
  - National Indian Family Preservation Conference, 1995; 1 box (Box 459)
  - Kellogg Foundation, Correspondence, Proposal, 1994; 1 box (Box 459)
  - Detail Gift Analysis List, 1995 January 1; 1 box (Box 459)
  - NYU Forum, 1994-1995; 1 box (Box 459)
  - National Support Council News, 1995 January; 1 box (Box 459)
  - The Educational Foundation of America Work, 1995; 1 box (Box 459)
  - Nonprofit Publications, 1994; 1 box (Box 459)
  - Native American Publications, 1994; 1 box (Box 459)
  - Public Service Directors of Network Television, undated; 1 box (Box 459)
  - Tristate Area Major Donors, 1994; 1 box (Box 459)
  - Articles on Native American Issues, circa 1994; 1 box (Box 459)